(Sheldon:)and solve the dark matter proton
decay problem at the same time.
(Amy:)Fine.
How was your day?
(Sheldon:)Oh, you said it.
(Leonard:)Sheldon.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I'm
worried about you.
(Amy:)You're not eating,
(Penny:)you haven't
slept in days,
(Amy:)and, to be honest, that
cap is starting to smell.
(Amy:)I know.
(Sheldon:)It's replaced Godzilla as
my principle source of anxiety.
(Howard:)Okay, so it's one vote Emily,
one vote Cinnamon.
(Howard:)Penny, you're
the tiebreaker.
(Penny:)Say the quote again.
"It's just so perfect
that we're both Libras."
(Penny:)Wow, this is hard.
(Penny:)I'm gonna say
Cinnamon.
Yes!
Come on!
(Howard:)That was the last one,
I promise.
We won't play anymore.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.